A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ditchley Foundation (London) (American Ditchley Foundation, New York), December 23, 1969-November 1, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 443)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Doa-Dom), December 14, 1948-Decemer 12, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 444)
- Dolkart, Ralph E., November 15, 1971-December 8, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 445)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Don-Dor), August 19, 1946-December 17, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 446)
- Donway, Walter, November 4, 1971-January 28, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 447)
- Donway, Walter (Personnel), May 25, 1972-June 22, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 448)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Dos-Doy), September 17, 1952-July 2, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 449)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Es-Ev), January 2, 1951-April 7, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 450)
- Esselstyn Foundation (Dr. and Mrs. Caldwell B. Esselstyn), December 11, 1951-October 20, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 451)
- Evans, Lester J., December 1, 1959-November 17, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 452)
- Evans, Lester J. (History of the Commonwealth Fund), December 27, 1977-July 2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 453)
- Evans, Lester J. (History of the Commonwealth Fund), December 27, 1977-July 2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 454)
- Evans, Lester J. (History of the Commonwealth Fund), December 27, 1977-July 2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 455)
- Evans, Lester J. (Trips), October 30, 1951-September 19, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 456)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ew-Ez), December 12, 1947-February 10, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 457)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Faa-Far), February 2, 1951-November 3, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 458)
- Fairleigh Dickinson University, March 3, 1967-April 5, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 459)
- Family Planning, August 10, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 460)
- Farnsworth, Dana L., April 21, 1953-September 21, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 461)
- Farr, C. Sims, December 13, 1973-December 23, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 462)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fas-Faz), March 21, 1949-October 25, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 463)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fea-Fel), March 23, 1951-June 17, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 464)
- Federal Medical Service Education, 1945-March 21, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 465)
- Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, April 2, 1951-September 13, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 466)
- Federation of World Health Foundations, April 22, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 467)
- Feldstein, Martin S. (Nuffield College, Oxford and Harvard University), August 22, 1961-June 16, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 468)
- Fels Research Institute for the Study of Human Development, March 7, 1955-September 28, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 469)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fen-Fez), March 9, 1951-April 22, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 470)
- Feshbach, Dan, April 15, 1977-May 3, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 471)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fia-Fir), March 30, 1951-November 17, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 472)
- Fieldhouse, Mrs. Alice, June 24, 1969-July 3, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 473)
- Fifth Avenue Association, October 17, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 474)
- Financing Private Colleges, October 18, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 475)
- Fine, Dr. Jacob (Performance in Surgical Disease of Hospitals in the U.S.), March 11, 1960-January 12, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 476)
- First National Conference on Evaluation in Public Health, August 12-18, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 477)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fit-Fiz), December 6, 1938-November 9, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 478)
- Fitz, Reginald, November 27, 1956-October 25, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 479)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fl), December 14, 1941-July 7, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 480)
- Fleschman Foundation, November 15-30, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 481)
- Flinders University of South Australia (G. J. Fraenkel), April 8, 1970-May 29, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 482)
- Florida Board of Regents, July 23, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 483)
- Florida State University, November 30, 1972-April 23, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 484)
- University of Florida (College of Medicine, Gainesville), November 9, 1967-December 17, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 485)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Foa-For), April 16, 1945-June 16, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 486)
- Forde, Richard J., August 13, 1976-September 28, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 487)
- Foreign Medical Graduates, March 20, 1969-April 4, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 488)
- Foreign Service Training Center, December 28, 1944-November 29, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 489)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fos-Foy), April 14, 1951-March 24, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 490)
- Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences, Inc. (Daniel Steinberg), February 21, 1966-April 28, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 491)
- Foundation for Child Development, September 29, 1972-February 21, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 492)
- Foundation for Human Ecology, January 9, 1961-March 30, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 493)
- Foundation Library Center, December 12, 1960-August 18, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 494)
- Foundation Library Center, December 12, 1960-August 18, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 495)
- Foundation Luncheon Group, March 22, 1972-February 9, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 496)
- Foundation Officers, May 20, 1975-January 10, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 497)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., July 1, 1968-April 19, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 498)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., July 1, 1968-April 19, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 499)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., July 1, 1968-April 19, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 500)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., May 4, 1974-October 6, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 501)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., May 4, 1974-October 6, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 502)
- Council on Foundations, Inc., May 4, 1974-October 6, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 503)
- Foundations Fund for Research in Psychiatry, June 12, 1957-January 21, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 504)
- Foundations Information Group, May 5, 1966-September 23, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 505)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fra), September 19, 1951-March 10, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 506)
- Framingham Study, February 8, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 507)
- Franklin and Marshall College, February 6, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 508)
- Franklin Book Program, Inc., January 14, 1953-March 20, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 509)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fre), June 4, 1951-December 1, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 510)
- French-Polyclinic Fund, Inc., July 18, 1968-September 16, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 511)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fri), February 28, 1951-January 23, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 512)
- Friends World College, January 4, 1978-January 23, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 513)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fro-Fry), February 27, 1951-January 21, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 514)
- Froedtert Memorial Lutheran Hospital, January 3-8, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 515)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Fu-Fy), January 24, 1949-January 29, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 516)
- Fund for Overseas Research Grants and Education, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 517)
- Fundacion Williams (de Thomas Jefferson Williams y Ana King de Williams), June 22, 1962-August 7, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 518)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gaa-Gal), January 1, 1947-December 31, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 519)
- Galdston, Iago, January 5, 1953-October 8, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 520)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gam-Gay), October 25, 1950-June 17, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 521)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gea-Gem), February 2, 1951-September 9, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 522)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gen-Gey), December 1, 1948-September 2, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 523)
- Genesee Hospital, December 27, 1971-January 4, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 524)
- University of Geneva, March 27, 1968-May 28, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 525)
- Georgetown University, June 1, 1956-November 23, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 526)
- Georgetown University, June 1, 1956-November 23, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 527)
- Georgia Institute of Technology, April 28, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 528)
- Gerontology-Geriatrics, January 25, 1954-November 14, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 529)
- Gerontology-Geriatrics (Mark Lipkin), March 7, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 530)
- Gerontology-Geriatrics (National Institute on Aging - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, National Institute of Health), July 22, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 531)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gia-Gil), November 30, 1951-May 15, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 532)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gin-Giz), December 6, 1948-February 10, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 533)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gl), February 1, 1952-April 7, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 534)
- Glaser, Robert J., November 27, 1956-November 13, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 535)
- Glasgow University, July 9, 1958-August 14, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 536)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Goa-Gol), March 8, 1951-June 10, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 537)
- Golden, William T. and William Goldfarb, August 20, 1970-November 10, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 538)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Ittleson Center for Child Research, Box 165, Folders 1526-1533.
- Goldstein, Avram (Principles of Drug Action), January 15, 1968-February 16, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 539)
- Golodetz, Arnold, May 2, 1968-October 5, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 540)
- Golovin, Nicholas E. (A "Fourth Branch" of Government), May 15, 1968-July 19, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 541)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gom-Goo), February 7, 1951-August 14, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 542)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gor-Goz), April 11, 1950-November 4, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 543)
- Gorsline, Lester, February 10, 1958-May 23, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 544)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Graa-Gram), November 11, 1949-July 31, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 545)
- Grace-New Haven Community Hospital, February 7, 1957-August 10, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 546)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gran-Grea), February 6, 1951-November 18, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 547)
- Greater Kansas City Mental Health Foundation, March 19, 1957-June 7, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 548)
- Greater New York Fund, March 7, 1954-February 4, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 549)
- Greater New York Hospital Association, November 19-22, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 550)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gree-Greu), January 23, 1950-May 23, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 551)
- Greenough, William C., February 25, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 552)
- Greulich, William Walter, September 29, 1960-February 2, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 553)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gri-Gry), September 19, 1951-December 11, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 554)
- Gross, Reuben H., November 4, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 555)
- Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry, February 24, 1959-September 29, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 556)
- Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry (Foreign Psychiatrists' Visits to the U.S. A.), September 26, 1949-February 17, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 557)
- Group Health Association of America, Inc., June 7, 1962-May 31, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 558)
- Group Health Insurance, August 29, 1969-March 13, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 559)
- Grunebaum, Henry, October 7, 1954-November 20, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 560)
- Grzegorzewski, Edward, November 26, 1965-December 2, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 561)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Gu-Gy), October 1, 1945-March 30, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 562)
- Guatemala University, July 23, 1967-May 11, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 563)
- Guttmacher, Alan F., December 6, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 564)
- Guttmacher Institute, March 25, 1970-May 9, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 565)
- Guy's Hospital Medical School (England), January 24, 1967-November 21, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 566)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Haa-Hal), February 11, 1949-February 12, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 567)
- Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital of Philadelphia (Joseph R. DiPalma), September 29, 1967-January 2, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 568)
- Hahnemann Medical College and Hospital of Philadelphia (Joseph R. DiPalma), September 29, 1967-January 2, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 569)
- Haile Selassie I University, December 7, 1962-December 2, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 570)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ham), February 16, 1951-July 15, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 571)
- Hamburg, David A., April 8, 1965-December 6, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 572)
- Hamdard National Foundation (Pakistan), April 14, 1972-September 11, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 573)
- Hampton Institute, March 7, 1955-January 3, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 574)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Han-Hap), April 17, 1951-March 27, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 575)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Harb-Harp), June 17, 1948-February 22, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 576)
- Harbury, Henry A. (Dartmouth Medical School, Department of Biochemistry), February 26, 1975-April 12, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 577)
- Harkness Community Hospital, September 26, 1967-July 7, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 578)
  Southern Pacific Memorial Hospitals, Inc. until 1968.
- Harkness Fellowship Program, October 1, 1968-September 10, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 579)
- Rebekah Harkness Foundation (School of Ballet), September 26, 1968-August 1, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 580)
- Harkness House (London, England), October 10, 1960-August 30, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 581)
- Harkness Pavilion (Queen's Medical Center, Honolulu, Hawaii), July 10, 1970-March 27, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 582)
- Harlem Hospital, December 12, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 583)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Harr-Hart), January 26, 1951-February 20, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 584)
- Harrington, Edwin, September 25, 1954-June 28, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 585)
- Harris, Michael (John Wiley and Sons, Inc.), December 4, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 586)
- Harrison, G. J., May 19, 1969-July 18, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 587)
- University of Hartford (Hospital), February 28, 1950-June 10, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 588)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Harv-Harw), January 24, 1952-October 25, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 589)
- Harvard University (McLean Hospital - Jordi Folchi-Pi), April 24, 1953-March 30, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 590)
- Harvard University Medical School, November 8, 1946-March 9, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 591)
- Harvard University Medical School, November 8, 1946-March 9, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 592)
- Harvard University Medical School, November 8, 1946-March 9, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 593)
- Harvard University Medical School, November 8, 1946-March 9, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 594)
- Harvard University Medical School (George S. Barry), August 18, 1954-July 3, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 595)
- Harvard University Medical School (George S. Barry), August 18, 1954-July 3, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 596)
- Harvard University Medical School (Edward Kass), October 21, 1972-March 27, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 597)
- Harvard University Medical School (Olser L. Peterson and John P. Bunker), April 12, 1974-September 11, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 598)
- Harvard University Medical School - Beth Israel Hospital (Ambulatory Care Service, Howard H. Hiatt), April 2-3, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 599)
- Harvard University Medical School - Beth Israel Hospital (Health Technology Laboratory, Howard H. Hiatt), May 21, 1971-January 27, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 600)
- Harvard University Medical School - Brigham Hospital, December 12, 1950-June 10, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 601)
- Harvard University Medical School - Curriculum Revision (Mark D. Altschule), January 6, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 602)
- Harvard University Medical School - Family Health Care Program (Charles A. Janeway), October 19, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 603)
- Harvard University Medical School - Health Care Standards and Measurements (David D. Rutstein), December 17, 1970-October 9, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 604)
- Harvard University Medical School - Health Care Standards and Measurements (David D. Rutstein), December 17, 1970-October 9, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 605)
- Harvard University Medical School - Health Care Standards and Measurements (David D. Rutstein), December 17, 1970-October 9, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 606)
- Harvard University Medical School - Health Careers Summer Program, July 3-16, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 607)
- Harvard University Medical School - International Medical School, March 23, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 608)
- Harvard University Medical School - Medicine in the Ghettos, February 18, 1969-December 13, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 609)
- Harvard University Medical School - Oral History Program (Leona Baugartner), January 2, 1973-April 24, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 610)
- Harvard University Medical School - Post Graduate Studies, June 13-19, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 611)
- Harvard University Medical School - Preventive Medicine, October 23, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 612)
- Harvard University - Pension Allotments, October 9, 1947-June 14, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 613)
- Harvard University Press, January 31, 1955-July 1, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 614)
- Harvard University School of Dental Medicine, September 4, 1970-July 9, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 615)
- Harvard University School of Public Health, January 14, 1953-February 29, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 616)
- Harvard University School of Public Health, January 14, 1953-February 29, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 617)
- Harvard University School of Public Health, January 14, 1953-February 29, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 618)
- Harvard University School of Public Health (Howard Hiatt), May 17, 1974-October 23, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 619)
- Harvard University School of Public Health - Center as Teaching-Training in Community Health Care, February 18, 1971-March 3, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 620)
- Harvard University School of Public Health - Center for Community Health and Medical Care (Paul M. Densen), November 8, 1972-September 17, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 621)
- Harvard University Sciences Center, October 24, 1949-May 24, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 622)
- Harvard University/Massachusetts General Hospital - Home Care Program, October 17, 1950-September 24, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 623)
- Harwood, Alan, February 24, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 624)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Has-Haz), October 29, 1951-April 2, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 625)
- University of Hawaii (School of Medicine), July 25, 1960-August 21, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 626)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Head-Health(P)), March 29, 1952-November 17, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 627)
- Health and Biomedical Planning Institute, July 24, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 628)
- Health and Hospital Planning Council of Southern New York, Inc., March 9, 1970-April 22, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 629)
- Health Care and Health Education, February 19, 1971-August 2, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 630)
- Health Data Management System (Denver), February 5, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 631)
- Health, Education and Population Dynamics, July 11, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 632)
- Health Insurance, February 18, 1970-July 13, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 633)
- Health Insurance (National), September 23, 1977-October 21, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 634)
- Health Maintenance Organization, April 1, 1972-February 10, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 635)
- Health Manpower, June 9, 1967-April 30, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 636)
- Bureau of Health Manpower (Joseph A. Gallagher), July 17, 1968-December 9, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 637)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Health (R)-Heg), April 1, 1951-February 12, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 638)
- Health Services Administration (New York City), August 24, 1967-November 26, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 639)
- Health Services and Education (General), April 11, 1957-August 8, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 640)
- Health Staff Seminar (George Washington University, Washington, D.C.), March 22, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 641)
- Heart House (Bethesda, Maryland; Dwight E. Harken), April 10, 1974-June 24, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 642)
- Hebrew University (Hadassah Medical School), October 6, 1954-August 10, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 643)
- Heffron, Roderick, April 16, 1968-December 30, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 644)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hei-Hel), February 22, 1951-January 16, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 645)
- Held, Philip J. (Urban Opinion Surveys, New Jersey), February 14, 1973-June 26, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 646)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hem-Hen), June 19, 1944-August 8, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 647)
- Hench, Ralph, March 2, 1971-December 15, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 648)
- Henshaw, Paul S., April 28, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 649)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Her-Hey), April 16, 1945-March 25, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 650)
- Hetzel, Basil S., November 18, 1952-May 16, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 651)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hia-Hil), December 16, 1947-December 22, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 652)
- Hiatt, Howard H., October 16, 1959-July 11, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 653)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Him-Hir), February 8, 1951-February 20, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 654)
- Lister Hill National Center for Biomedical Communications (Ralph P. Christenson), July 19, 1967-February 6, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 655)
- Hiltner, Seward, December 21, 1953-April 5, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 656)
- Cross Reference Sheets (His-Hit), November 26, 1946-August 14, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 657)
- Mary Hitchcock Memorial Clinic, April 6, 1951-May 14, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 658)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hoa-Hof), May 17, 1951-July 17, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 659)
- Hock, Raymond J., May 11, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 660)
- Hoffman, Francisco, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 661)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hog-Hok), January 8, 1952-May 17, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 662)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hola-Hols), July 28, 1950-October 15, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 663)
- Holden, William (Case Western Reserve University, Medical School), May 14, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 664)
- Hollaender, Alexander, March 27, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 665)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Holt-Hop), November 28, 1951-March 28, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 666)
- Holt, Samuel C. O., May 9-14, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 667)
- Holton, Gerald (Harvard University, Department of Physics), December 9, 1971-July 1, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 668)
- Home of the Merciful Saviour for Crippled Children, December 30, 1955-January 17, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 669)
- Hoover Commission Report (Federal Medical Service), January 28, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 670)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hor), October 1, 1951-February 12, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 671)
- Karen Horney Foundation, December 1, 1952-March 25, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 672)
- Horwitz, Samuel, April 3, 1951-October 1, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 673)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hos-Hou), November 28, 1949-January 5, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 674)
- Hospital Council of Greater New York, August 9, 1950-January 16, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 675)
- Hospital Research and Educational Trust (Illinois), July 20, 1964-June 7, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 676)
- Cross Reference Sheets (How-Hoy), September 21, 1949-May 24, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 677)
- Howard University, October 10, 1961-November 17, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 678)
- Howard University, October 10, 1961-November 17, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 679)
- Hsueh, Mingsin, December 6, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 680)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hua-Hul), September 4, 1951-April 15, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 681)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hum-Hun), February 6, 1951-May 5, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 682)
- Human Dimensions in Medical Education (Orienne Strode), March 13, 1973-December 7, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 683)
- Hunnybun, N. K., July 7, 1969-September 29, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 684)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hur-Huy), October 27, 1950-January 14, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 685)
- Huxley Institute for Biosocial Research (Saskatchewan), October 26, 1972-December 29, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 686)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Hy), March 2, 1951-April 9, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 687)
- Hyman, Edward, June 3, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 688)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ib-Im), October 24, 1950-November 9, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 689)
- University of Ibadan, March 13, 1963-February 6, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 690)
- Idaho Foundation for Medicine and Biology, February 5, 1966-October 3, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 691)
- Idaho State University, July 26-30, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 692)
- Idant Corporation (Blood Survey and Washed Red Cell Program), August 9, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 693)
- Illinois Health Education Commission, August 24, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 694)
- Illinois Institute of Technology, March 3, 1965-March 2, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 695)
- University of Illinois (College of Medicine), December 8, 1947-December 14, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 696)
- University of Illinois (College of Medicine - Center for Study of Patient Care and Community Health), January 16-22, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 697)
- University of Illinois (College of Medicine) - Urban Campaign, November 6, 1969-July 3, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 698)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Inc-Insl), September 25, 1944-January 15, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 699)
- Independent Citizens Research Foundation (New York), February 20, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 700)
- Indiana University, April 12, 1951-April 30, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 701)